

Grayson

Taylor

Contact

Address:

Salontie 49, Helsinki, Finland

Email:

champion5star247963@gmail.com

Skype:

live:.cid.e07bcb612fe88d1b

Skills

- React.js
- React Native
- Vue.js
- Express.js
- Django
- Laravel
- Node.js
- Javascript
- Typescript
- Python
- PHP
- MongoDB
- PostgreSQL
- MySQL

Language

English C1

Summary

Senior full-stack developer with over 10 years of experience in software development across various industries, with the 5 most recent years focused on React and TypeScript. I am well-respected amongst industry-leading companies as a skilled developer who truly understands the client infrastructure and pain points. I also have the hands-on, technical aptitude needed to design and build out solutions.

Skill Highlights

- User familiar UX/UI
- API building and Integration
- Soket IO
- Database design
- Good communication

Experience

Senior Software Engineer - 04/2019 to 03/2022

ASPIRITY, San Francisco, United States

- Served as a second developer on a system modernization project.
- Built the app architecture and design system components.
- Conducted R&D (research and development) for libraries and ways to improve our codebase. Helped and mentored junior developers from various backgrounds.

Full Stack Engineer - 07/2015 to 07/2018

NATURAILY, San Diego, United States

- Maintained and improved the client portal React application.
- Implemented workflows and guidelines for code consistency, readability, maintainability, and testability.
- Refactored and upgraded the continuous integration code of our main repository and created a gem to make available to other projects.

Education

Bachelor of Degree in **Computer Science** - 2013 **Helsinki University**, Helsinki, Finland 2008 - 2013

Certification

Certified Web and Mobile Application Developer

Provider: SMTP Issued: January 2020